SPEAKER_00:  Ravi, bring me a cup of coffee.
SPEAKER_00:  So, what?
SPEAKER_01:  No.
SPEAKER_01:  Hey Shetty!
SPEAKER_01:  You have two options.
SPEAKER_01:  Leave us.
SPEAKER_01:  You'll get so much money that you won't have a place to stay in this police station.
SPEAKER_01:  Welcome to our Channel.
SPEAKER_02:  Welcome to our Channel.
SPEAKER_01:  And the second option
SPEAKER_01:  Thank you for watching.
SPEAKER_02:  You won't be able to save this police station.
SPEAKER_02:  You don't know her.
SPEAKER_00:  Threatening me?
SPEAKER_00:  You are talking about Danger Langa, right?
SPEAKER_00:  Who is he?
SPEAKER_00:  I know.
SPEAKER_00:  The real danger
SPEAKER_00:  is waiting for you.
SPEAKER_01:  Every officer who wears uniform thinks he is Singham.
SPEAKER_00:  Arararara
SPEAKER_00:  No, dad.
SPEAKER_00:  He is our Guruji.
SPEAKER_00:  I am not a Singham.
SPEAKER_00:  I am Lady Singham.